<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tech Samskruthi</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tech Samskruthi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 04:48:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CRED</title>
      <link>/posts/episode-2-cred/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 04:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/episode-2-cred/</guid>
      <description>In this episode we talk about CRED (https://www.cred.club/) app and recent talk news.
Overview CRED is a fintech startup founded in 2018 in Bangalore, India by Kunal Shah. Their main business idea is around helping customers benefit by earning reward points on making credit card payments through the CRED app.
Funding Seed round was from Sequoia India, Ribbit and RTP global. They are currently in series B with raising $4M in the latest round as of this writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Tech Samskruthi</title>
      <link>/posts/welcome-to-tech-samskruthi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 04:48:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/welcome-to-tech-samskruthi/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Tech Samskruthi platform! We talk about Technology, Startups, Venture Capital, Gaming and everything in between! All in Kannada. Please stay tuned!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Tech Samskruthi is a platform created by Shashank Kumar Shankar and Nithin Kashyap where they talk about technology, startups, venture capital and other fun stuff in a language called Kannada native to state of Karnataka, India.
More about Shashank Shashank works in Silicon Valley, California in one of the FAANG companies. His domain expertise is around building cloud / AI platforms.
More about Nithin Nithin works in Las Vegas, Nevada in a company which validates autonomous vehicle technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description> YouTube channel: https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCSg8vJkjfI1_KsctF_CV_8g
Email: techsamskruthi@gmail.com
Shashank&amp;rsquo;s Email: shank4804@gmail.com
Nithin&amp;rsquo;s Email: nithinkashyap26@gmail.com
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
